A Finding Aid to the Paul Bransom Papers, 1862-1985, bulk 1904-1979, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, circa 1903-1984; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 4.5 Linear feet Box 1-5
  - General Correspondence, 1961; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 24-27)
  - General Correspondence, 1962; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
  - General Correspondence, 1963; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders) (Box 2, Folder 30-35)
  - General Correspondence, 1964; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders) (Box 2, Folder 36-41)
  - General Correspondence, 1965; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - General Correspondence, 1966; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - General Correspondence, 1967; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - General Correspondence, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1969; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - General Correspondence, 1970; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 12-15)
  - General Correspondence, 1971; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
  - General Correspondence, 1972; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 19-23)
  - General Correspondence, 1973; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 24-25)
  - General Correspondence, 1974; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 26-30)
  - General Correspondence, 1975; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 31-35)
  - General Correspondence, 1976; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 36-39)
  - General Correspondence, 1977; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence, 1978; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 3-5)
  - General Correspondence, 1979; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
  - General Correspondence, 1980-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, A-B, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, C-F, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, G-H, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, I-L, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, M, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, N-R, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, S-Y, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, First Names Only, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Drafts of Letters by Paul Bransom, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Cards, Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Paul Bransom's Outgoing Christmas Cards, circa 1930, 1963-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Paul Bransom's Outgoing Christmas Cards (Duplicates), 1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Wendy Astley-Bell, 1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
      (Contains original artwork)
    - Alice Atkinson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous A, 1955-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Wladislaw, Romola, and Emilia Benda, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous B, 1953-1978, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
      (Contains cards made by Harry Beckhoff, Frank Bensing, Ed Bierly, Walter Biggs, Pat Bott, Bob Brikerhoff, and Joseph Burgess)
    - Chen Chi, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Chen Chi (Duplicates), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous C, 1956-1979, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 30-31)
      (Contains cards made by Harrison Cady, Bob Carroll, Charles Chapman, John Clymer, Kent Day Coes, Farrell Collett, Elizabeth Cowan, and a photograph of John Clymer)
    - Gerard Curtis Delano, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Rita Duis (Astley-Bell), 1971-1980, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous D, 1961-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
      (Contains cards made by Bob Davenport, Joe Davis, Gladdys Davis, and Charles DeFeo)
    - Miscellaneous E, 1950-1977, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
      (Contains cards made by Rosalie Edge)
    - Miscellaneous F, 1963-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
      (Contains cards made by Bill Freeman, O.E. von Feuher, and Elisabeth Fulda)
    - Miscellaneous G, 1957-1977, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
      (Contains cards mdae by Rube Goldberg, Frank Gervasi, and Al Gilbert)
    - Malthe Hasselriis, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous H, 1954-1974, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39-40)
      (Contains cards made by Grant Hagen, Charles Hargens, John Hamburger, Helen Ireland Hays, Lynn Bogue Hunt, and photographs of Frank and Brownie Hibben)
    - Miscellaneous I-J, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
      (Contains cards made by Helen Ingliss, Joseph C. Jones, Anders Jordahl, and Hazel Brill Jackson)
    - Bob and Dorie Kane, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Bob Kuhn, 1963-1974, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Walt Kuhn, 1940, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous K, 1977-1978, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
      (Contains cards made by Phil Kappel, Isabelle Knobloch, and Les Kouba)
    - Miscellaneous L, 1959-1981, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
      (Contains cards made by Jack Lehrer, Dorothy Lathrop, William R. Leigh, Kay Lichty, and an original drawing by Bob Lougheed)
    - Ugo and Edna Mochi, 1974-1980, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Benson Moore, 1969, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Benson Moore (Duplicates), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Scope and Contents
    - Miscellaneous M, 1962-1980, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
      (Contains cards made by Joseph Margulies, Dorcas MacClintock, Don Miller, and Olaus Murie)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1981, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
      (Contains cards made by A. Henry Nordhausen)
    - Tom Olenchak, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous O-R, 1967-1968, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
      (Contains cards made by Karl Plath and O. Plancy)
    - Charles Sarka, 1938, 1957, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - William Schaldach, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Conrad Schwiering, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Bob Scriver, 1970, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Alexander Seidel, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Bob Sleicher, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - The Streeters, 1958-1978, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Tom Suggs, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous S, 1967-1978, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
      (Contains cards made by Lloyd Sandford, Tona Soglow, Ben Stahl, the Spiro's, and Dolf Swing)
    - Kilpurdy Tee-Van, 1965-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Clarence Tillenius, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Wayne Trimm, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous T, 1932, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
      (Contains cards made by Don Teague, Anice and Albert Payson Terhune, and Ed Tomasieriez)
    - Wheeler Williams, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - James Perry Wilson, 1957-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous V-Z, 1955-1975, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
      (Contains cards made by Pietro Valerio, Vilma and F. Warren, Ernest Watson, Katherine Lane Weems, Grant Hagen, and William Zimmerman)
    - Miscellaneous First Names Only, 1962-1978, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30-32)
- Notes and Writings, circa 1927-1973; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 0.2 Linear feet Box 5, OV 12
  This small series includes a diary, notebooks, essays, lists, notes, and other writings by Paul Bransom and others. The diary, with notes, writings, and sketches, was written during a hunting expedition Bransom made with writer J. Frank Dobie in 1927. Other writings in this folder include an eight page essay recounting the hunt by G.W. "Dub" Evans. Four notebooks contain miscellaneous notes on travel expenses, contact information, drafts of outgoing letters, and pressed flowers. Biographical, historical, nature, and art writings include brief essays and notes for talks by Bransom and others about his career, the lives of fellow artists, animals and animal art, and a satirical essay about modern art. Notes by and about Walt Kuhn include an essay by Bransom, comments by Bransom on a journal article about Kuhn, and a sketchbook with visual notes made by Kuhn during a discussion with Paul and Grace Bransom.
  Notes on animals and artwork include research notes, ideas for illustrations and stories, and technical notes about artwork. Also found are lists of private collectors of Bransom's work and notes on members of the Jackson Hole, Wyoming, community. Miscellaneous notes concern books, music, spiritual musings, inspirational quotes from published sources, and notes related to items in this collection which have become separated from those items. A folder of poems inspired by Bransom and his paintings, many of which were written by friends for Bransom's birthday, is also present, as well as a photocopy of an inventory from an unknown repository of papers related to H.C. Pitz.
  Additional biographical notes and writings concerning Bransom and his career can be found in Biographical Materials. Additional notes pertaining to professional projects and financial matters can be found in Personal Business Records.
  - Diary and Other Writings, New Mexico Lion Hunt (See also Artwork), 1927-1928; Archival Resource Key; (includes sketches) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Notebooks, 1950-1959, 1971, undated; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 5, Folder 34-37)
  - Biographical, Historical, Nature, and Art Writing, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Notes on Animals and Artwork, 1972, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Notes by and about Walt Kuhn, 1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Private Collectors of Bransom, 1965, 1969, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Jackson Hole People and Dude Ranches, 1973, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1972, 1973, undated; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Poems by Friends and Admirers, 1970, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - H.C. Pitz Inventory, undated; Archival Resource Key; (photocopy, not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Oversized Miscellaneous Notes (See Box 5, f42), Archival Resource Key (Oversize 12)
- Personal Business Records, circa 1912-1981; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 0.3 Linear feet Box 5
  This series includes records relating to Bransom's illustration and advertising clients, galleries where he exhibited, other Bransom projects, bibliographies and inventories of Bransom's artwork, and records of projects of family members. Arrangement is alphabetical by gallery or business entity, with special subjects placed at the end of the series. Types of records include correspondence, receipts, lists, notes, contracts, pamphlets, and brochures.
  Gallery and illustration client records document exhibitions, consignments, and sales of Bransom's artwork. The files for Teton Artists Associated also contain Bransom's designs for brochures and advertisements, proofs of printed materials, a contract, and lists of students. The file for Northwest Schools contains a contract for the production of an instructional book on animal drawing by Bransom, as well as correspondence related to the project. For a copy of that publication, see Printed Materials.
  Also found are bibliographies compiled by Seth Mattingly and Helen Ireland Hays, and an artwork inventory compiled by Mario Cesar Romero after Bransom's death. Drafts of Mattingly's bibliographies are found with his correspondence in Series 1. Additional correspondence related to Bransom's business activities, including magazine and book illustrations, exhibitions, and other business with entities listed in this series can also be found in the Correspondence series. Exhibition Catalogs and other printed materials related to exhibitions can be found in Printed Materials.
  - Abercrombie and Fitch, 1939-1941, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Morris L. Appleman, Denver Exhibition, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Artists Day at Christmas Sales for the Blind, 1954-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1931-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - General Store Gallery, 1970-1971, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Grand Central Galleries, 1966-1973, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Hawley Advertising Company, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Lord and Thomas Advertising, 1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Northwest Schools, Inc., 1961-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Royal Ontario Museum, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Seagram Distillers Company, 1956-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Society of Illustrators, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Teton Artists Associated, 1958-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 58-59)
  - The Toronto Star, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Woodmere Art Gallery, 1962-1964, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Notices of Receipt for Artwork, 1925, 1964-1979, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 62)
    (Contains records from Arden Studios, Inc., The James Ford Bell Museum of Natural History in Minnesota, the Fulton County Museum, and the Brandywine River Museum)
  - Miscellaneous Consignments and Sales, 1942-1980, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1912-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Personal Financial Records, 1924, 1949, 1962-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Grace Bransom's Doll Business, 1953, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Harry Bond's Invention, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Bibliography of Illustrations, 1980, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Bibliography and Artwork Inventory, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Artwork Inventory Project Notes, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Artwork Inventory, circa 1981; Archival Resource Key; (7 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-7)
- Printed Materials, circa 1905-1985; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 1.5 Linear feet Boxes 6-7, OV 12
  This series includes catalogs and announcements for exhibitions; reproductions of Bransom illustrations and cartoons from magazines, newspapers, and calendars; newspaper and magazine articles about Bransom and others; programs from musical events in which Bransom performed; newsletters, brochures, membership directories, mailings, and invitations from organizations in which Bransom was involved; pamphlets and other printed matter about Jack London and other people known to Bransom; and a copy of Bransom's art technique book, Animal Drawing.
  Catalogs are for individual and group exhibitions of Bransom's artwork, some of which are annotated with prices and other information. Printed price lists, press releases, and invitations are also found. Selected catalogs of exhibitions by Walt Kuhn and his pupil, Lily Cushing are filed under their names.
  Many of Bransom's illustrations for magazine stories are also found, including stories by writers Albert Payson Terhune and Jim Corbett. An early newspaper cartoon series by Bransom called "News From Bugville" is represented here by over 200 printed copies of cartoons. An original drawing from Bransom's cartoon series is found in Artwork.
  Clippings include biographies, reviews of exhibitions, book reviews for books illustrated by Bransom, obituaries, and other news related to Bransom and his friends. Additional clippings are found in Scrapbooks, and scattered clippings are found in Correspondence.
  Printed material related to organizations ranges from a single item to long runs of newsletters or catalogs, with occasional annotations by Bransom and others. The Salmagundi Club and the Society of Animal Artists have the widest range of materials, including newsletters, announcements, exhibition documentation, membership directories, and other mailings. See also Personal Business Records for original records of Bransom's transactions with some of the organizations listed here.
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - Paul Bransom, 1929-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      partially scanned
    - Paul Bransom, 1962-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
      (partially scanned)
    - Paul Bransom, 1970-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Paul Bransom, 1980-1983, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Paul Bransom (Duplicates), 1931-1979, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Lily Cushing, 1947; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Walt Kuhn, 1927-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Illustrations by Paul Bransom, 1925-1939; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Illustrations by Paul Bransom, 1942-1979; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Illustrations by Paul Bransom, undated; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Illustrations by Paul Bransom, Printers' Proofs, 1925, undated; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Reproductions of Artwork by Other Artists, undated; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Bugs in Bugville and Other Cartoons by Paul Bransom, 1905-1909, undated; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders) (Box 6, Folder 21-26)
  - Clippings about Paul Bransom, 1921-1929; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Clippings about Paul Bransom, 1935-1948; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Clippings about Paul Bransom, 1950-1969; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Clippings about Paul Bransom, 1970-1985; Archival Resource Key; (See also OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Clippings about Paul Bransom, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Clippings about Paul Bransom, Duplicates, 1947-1948, 1967; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Clippings about Walt Kuhn, 1920-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Clippings about Other Artists and Friends of Paul Bransom, 1965-1976, undated; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Music Concerts and Recitals, 1908; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Organizations, Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 6)
    - Artists' Fellowship, Inc., 1974-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - American Artists Professional League, 1962-1978; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 37-38)
    - American Watercolor Society, 1959-1978; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 39-41)
    - Dutch Treat Club, 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Grand Central Art Galleries, 1965-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
    - Jackson Hole Fine Arts Foundation, 1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - New York Water Color Club, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Salmagundi Club, 1950-1985, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8-11)
    - Society of Animal Artists, 1962-1985, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12-14)
    - Sportsman's Edge, Ltd., 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 15-17)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations, 1951-1981, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
      (Includes materials related to Bear Paw Ranch; the Junior Literary Guild; the Burroughs Nature Study Club; The Eccentric Club of Gloversville, NY; the National Advertising Art Center, Inc.; the National Amateur Art Festival; the National Society of Arts and Letters; Weber State College; the Boone and Crockett Club; and the International Platform Association)
  - People, Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 7)
    - Jack London, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Other Artists and Friends, 1947-1976, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Publications, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Animal Drawing by Paul Bransom, undated; Archival Resource Key; (See OV 12) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "Story of the Armory Show" by Walt Kuhn, 1938; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Oversized Printed Material, Archival Resource Key; (See Box 6, f16-20, 27-30; and Box 7, f21) (Oversize 12)
- Photographs, circa 1885-1976; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 7-8, 10
  This series includes photographs depicting Bransom, his family, other artists, pets and other animals, homes and studios, landscapes, trips, events, and works of art. Many of the photographs in this series have identifications on them, some of which appear to have been made retrospectively by Bransom. Other identifications appear to be in the handwriting of his niece and heiress, Althea Bond; and Mario Cesar Romero, who signed his notes "MCR."
  Wherever possible, photographs which appear to have been taken and printed together have been filed together. Numerous photographs of Bransom painting and drawing are found in this series. See folder notes below and notes on the photographs themselves for additional information about content.
  The slide album has been re-housed for preservation, but the original arrangement of the slides in their sleeves has been preserved. Images in the slide album include Paul and Grace Bransom, their Canada Lake and Jackson Hole homes, landscapes in the Adirondack and Teton mountains, Bransoms' friends, Paul Bransom painting in the studio and outside, and nature photographs labeled "studies for paintings." Most of the slides are Kodachrome and have suffered very little fading.
  Additional photographs are found in Scrapbooks, and scattered photographs are found in Correspondence. See the series description for further details.
  - Portraits of Paul Bransom, 1940-1973, undated; Archival Resource Key; (See also Box 10) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Portraits of Paul Bransom (Duplicates), circa 1940-1973, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Early Photographs of Paul Bransom (See also Scrapbooks), 1910, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25-26)
    (Also pictured is Bransom's sister Mary)